Now, here's a potential problem with Decision Trees.
现在我们来看看决策树中潜在的问题
Let's say we have a humungous table with lots and lots of columns.
比如说我们有一张极大的表格 其中行列很多
So, we create our Decision Tree and let's say it looks like this.
然后我们建立了决策树  比如说是这个样子的
This is not a realistic tree, though, just an example.
这只是一个例子 并不是真实的决策树
And we end up with answers like the following.
然后我们得到了如下结论
If a client is male between 15 and 25 in the US,
如果一位客户为男性 年龄在 15 到 25 之间 居住在美国
on Android, in school,
使用 Android 还在上学
likes tennis, pizza, but does not like long walks on the beach,
喜欢网球和披萨 但不喜欢长时间在沙滩上长散步
then they're likely to download Pokemon Go.
那么他很可能下载 Pokemon Go
This is not good. This almost looks like the tree just memorized the data.
这种做法很不理想 看起来似乎只是在记忆数据
It's overfitting. Decision Trees tend to overfit a lot.
这种情况称为过拟合 决策树经常会过拟合
In the continuous case, this can also happen and it looks like this.
如果我们选用连续特征也会出现这种问题
The Decision Tree has many nodes which end up giving us
决策树有许多结点 它最终会呈现给我们多个几乎与点相接的小方块
a complicated boundary that pretty much borders every point with a small square.
这些小方块将不同颜色的点分开
This is also overfitting as it doesn't generalize well to the data.
这也是过拟合现象 因为它对数据不具备普适性
So, how do we solve this? In the simplest possible way. Take a look at this.
那么如何解决这一问题呢  方法很简单
Let's take our data and say,
我们可以这样操作
pick some of the columns randomly.
随机从数据中挑选几列
Build a Decision Tree in those columns.
并根据这些列建构决策树
Now, pick some other columns randomly and build
然后随机选取其它几列
a Decision Tree in those, and do it again.
再次构建决策树
And now, just let the trees vote.
然后让决策树进行选择
When we have a new data point,
当我们有新的数据时
say this person over here,
比如说出现了一个新用户
we just let all the trees make a prediction and pick the one that appears the most.
就只需让所有的决策树做出预测 并选取结果中显示最多的
For example, these trees decided that
比如 这些决策树觉得
this person will download Snapchat, WhatsApp, and WhatsApp.
这个人会下载 Snapchat WhatsApp 和 WhatsApp
So, the ensemble of trees will recommend WhatsApp.
因此 决策树的集成会推荐此人下载 WhatsApp
Since we used a bunch of trees on randomly picked columns,
由于我们利用随机的列建构的多个决策树做出了预测
this is called a random forest.
这种方法称为随机森林
There are better ways to pick the columns than randomly and we'll
其实还有比随机选取列更好的方法
see this in the ensemble methods section of this Nanodegree.
我们将在该纳米课程的集成方法部分进行学习